https://lhsa.org/lhsa-privacy-policy/

HomeAbout Us/JoinJoin TodayMission Statement & VisionAbout LHSA – The International Leica SocietyEvent CalendarLHSA Philanthropy FundLHSA Privacy PolicyDonate to LHSAContact UsOfficersMy AccountLog InViewfinderViewfinder Archives & MoreCamera ReviewsHistorical ArticlesTips & TechniquesTravel ArticlesUpcoming EventsEvent CalendarLHSA MarketplaceLHSA StoreLHSA Buy and Sell (Members Only)Browse AdsCancel PaymentEdit AdLHSA CommunityAsk An Expert!Q & A from Ask an ExpertLHSA Webinar RecordingsLEICA FIRMWARE UpdatesLHSA Member Discounts for Leica Akademie USA WorkshopsMember DirectoryMember Discounts on Leica Camera RepairLHSA Philanthropy FundActivity FeedResourcesViewfinder Archives & MoreMust ReadPresident's Message December 2020Leica Announces the New Leica SL2-S5 Rare Off-Brand Screw Mount Lenses for Classic LeicasRestoring an 85-Year-Old Leica CameraLHSA Webinar RecordingsLeica x Oberwerth Black Friday & Cyber Monday PromotionSupport Photography this #GivingTuesdayNew Product Announcement: Leica Q2 MonochromLocating Long Lost Leicas by the numbers...Special Membership Offer for Leica ConversationsIntroducing the Sustaining Membership LevelLHSA Announces the 2020 Photo Grant RecipientFree Webinar: Jan 27 Photographic Prints and the Digital Era with Philip BlairCongratulations to the Fall 2020 Sweepstakes WinnersAll That Glitters is not ChromeLHSA - 2020 Officer, Board of Directors and ByLaw Change ElectionsRemembering Heidi SchneiderChanging of the GuardRECOLLECTIONS OF KNUTNew Orleans Portrayed
HomeAbout Us/JoinJoin TodayMission Statement & VisionAbout LHSA – The International Leica SocietyEvent CalendarLHSA Philanthropy FundLHSA Privacy PolicyDonate to LHSAContact UsOfficersMy AccountLog InViewfinderViewfinder Archives & MoreCamera ReviewsHistorical ArticlesTips & TechniquesTravel ArticlesUpcoming EventsLeica AkademieFree Webinar Nov. 18: Taking Infrared Photos with the Leica...Aug 19, 2020Miami - Dawn and Dusk: Feb 21-23, 2020Dec 9, 2019Leika Akademie Singapore: Understanding the SL - Dec 7Oct 26, 2019Event CalendarCheck out our full event calendarEvent CalendarLHSA MarketplaceLHSA StoreLHSA Buy and Sell (Members Only)Browse AdsCancel PaymentEdit AdLHSA CommunityAsk An Expert!Q & A from Ask an ExpertLHSA Webinar RecordingsLEICA FIRMWARE UpdatesLHSA Member Discounts for Leica Akademie USA WorkshopsMember DirectoryMember Discounts on Leica Camera RepairLHSA Philanthropy FundActivity FeedResourcesViewfinder Archives & More Home LHSA Privacy PolicyLHSA Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices
for The International Leica Society (“LHSA”, “we” or “us”). It applies to
information collected [via subscriptions, forms, email, live events, website
usage or other direct contact], and will provide you with information relating
to the personal identifiable information we collect including (but not limited
to) the following:What personal identifiable information is collected from you, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.What information do
we collect?We are the sole owners (and controller) of the information
collected. We will collect, use, process, store and transfer different kinds of
personal data you voluntarily give us via subscriptions, forms, email, live
events, website usage or other direct contact from you.We collect information such as your name and contact
information (such as your email address, phone number, postal address) from you
when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form online. We may collect
additional information during live events.If you make a purchase through our websites, our third-party
payment processor service providers may also collect billing information, such
as your first and last name, email address, phone number, credit card or debit
card number, and billing and shipping addresses. If you make a purchase over
the phone, we will collect this personal information and share it with our
third-party payment processor service providers.How do we use your information?We collect, process and disclose your personal data only for
specific and limited purposes. Your information may be used to send you
information and updates such as new blog posts, company news, updates, related
product or service information and facilitate communication. We will use your
information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will
not share your information with any third party outside of our organization
other than as necessary to fulfill your request. We may share your personal
information with our agents or contractors in connection with services that
these individuals or entities perform for LHSA. These agents or contractors are
not authorized by us to use or disclose this information except as necessary to
provide services for LHSA. We may, for example, provide your information to
agents or contractors for hosting our databases, for data processing services, for
marketing purposes, for organizing events, for processing online, or so that
they can mail you information you requested. We may share your personal
information in order to comply with the law, or protect ours or others’ rights,
property, or safety. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will ask you to opt-in so that we may contact you via
email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or
changes to this Privacy Policy.We may use your personal information to analyze the use of
our website content, services and events, in order to improve them, to develop
new content and services and to predict future customer behavior, as part of
our legitimate interests as a not-for profit
membership organization engaged in the sale of products and services in
furtherance of the organization’s purposes.The email address you provide may be used to send you
information and updates such as new blog posts, company news, updates, related
product or service information.The legal basis for processing your personal information
includes one or more of the following:Processing is
necessary for the performance of a contract with in order to take steps at the
request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract with youProcessing is
necessary for the purpose of the legitimate interest pursued by LHSA as the
controller or by a third party;You have given
consent;Processing is
necessary for compliance with a legal obligation;Processing is
necessary in order to protect yours or any others’ vital interest.How do we protect
your information?Only LHSA headquarters or trusted third parties who assist
us in conducting our business, who need the information to perform a specific
job are granted access to personally identifiable information.We maintain administrative, technical and physical
safeguards for the website designed to protect against loss, misuse or
unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the information
we collect through our website.How long do we keep your personal
information?We will retain your personal information while we are using
it, and may continue to retain it after these uses have ended where we have a
legitimate business purpose. For example, if you have opted out of marketing
communications from us, we will retain limited details about you to ensure the
opt-out request is honored. We may also continue to retain your personal
information to meet our legal requirements or to defend or exercise our legal
rights.Your Access to and Control
Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.Your legal rights are as follows:Access to a copy of
your personal information;Objection to the
processing of your personal information;Objection to
automated decision-making and profiling;Restriction of
processing your personal information;Your personal
information portability;Rectification of your
personal information;Erasure of your
personal information; andWithdrawal of the
consent to the processing of your personal information (if the processing is
based on this consent).In some cases, these rights are subject to conditions and
limitations.You can exercise any of your rights at any time by
contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our contact
page. We will consider such requests in accordance with all applicable data
protection laws and regulations.Do we use cookies?We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data
stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our
site and identify repeat visitors to our site.  Cookies can also enable us
to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our
site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable
information on our site. We use the following cookies:
Google Analytics.Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies; you can set the
browser to accept or reject all or certain types of the cookies at any time
even if after you have consented to our use of cookies by using our website.
Please note that you may not be able to receive certain services on this
website if you refuse a cookie. If you require further information you could
visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ .Third-party LinksOur website may contain links to other websites. These
websites are not under our control and will likely have their own privacy
policies.  You acknowledge that your use of and access to these websites
are solely at your risk, and that it is your responsibility to check the
privacy notices of these websites. International Data TransferAs an international organization and
because of the technologies we use, personal information may be transferred to
the United States and to other countries, which may not have the same data
protection laws as the country in which you reside.In cases of transfers from the European Union, the European
Economic Area or Switzerland to the United States, information is transferred,
stored and processed in accordance to appropriate safeguards approved by the
European Commission.Changes to our Privacy PolicyWe
reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time.  If
we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this
page. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we
treat your information, including by placing a prominent notice on our website
or by sending you an email so that you can choose whether to continue using the
website.  Material modifications are
effective 30 calendar days after our initial notification or upon your
acceptance of the modified terms.  Immaterial
modifications are effective upon posting of the updated Privacy Policy on our
website.  Please revisit this page
periodically to stay aware of any changes to this Privacy Policy.Dispute ResolutionPlease contact us if you believe that LHSA has not adhered
to this Privacy Policy. We will respond to you within the maximum time limit
prescribed by applicable law upon receipt of your correspondence and will do
our best to address your concerns. You may also report privacy complaints to your
relevant local data protection authority.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy,
you may contact us at info@lhsa.org . You may also
contact our Data Protection Officer directly:Richard Rejino, LHSA Executive DirectorAddress: 14070 Proton Rd. Suite 100, Dallas, TX 75244Phone: +1 972-233-9107 Recent PostsPresident's Message December 2020Dec 10, 20200Leica Announces the New Leica SL2-SDec 10, 202005 Rare Off-Brand Screw Mount Lenses for Classic LeicasDec 7, 20200Who’s Online There are no users currently onlineTags50mm Adobe Apo-Macro-Elmarit-R Apo-Summicron ASPH Bokeh Elmar Historical Iceland Japan Landscape Leica Akademie Leicaflex SL Leica III Leica IIIC Leica M Leica M-D Leica M6 Leica M9 Leica M Monochrom (Typ 240) Leica M Monochrom (Typ 246) Leica Q Leica S Leica S (Typ 007) Leica T Leica X Vario Leitz lenses lightroom Macro-Elmar-M M Lenses News Noctilux Nokton olympics Review Summarit Summaron Summicron Summilux Taylor-Hobson Tips & Techniques Travel Vario-Elmar-S Visoflex II Visoflex III
Copyright 2016 LHSA All Right Reserved. Back to top
Powered By Ultimate Auction
